{
    "id": "6716991b939946ff8f5b0dee9079244f",
    "title": "Conjunction And Relative Pronouns Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "376a45eccae74a158f5a20ab514393a8",
            "title": "Conjunctions And Relative Pronouns Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "……………………… she was ill, she could not go to school.",
                    "description": "As gives the reason. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "As",
                        "If",
                        "As if"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is a rich woman ........................ she does not help anyone.",
                    "description": "But is used to connect two contrasting ideas. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "and",
                        "who",
                        "but"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Stand up .......................... speak for yourself.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "and",
                        "if",
                        "when"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… she said made no sense to me.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "What",
                        "That",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is an atheist ……………………. does not believe in the existence of God.",
                    "description": "Use who to refer to people.",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "whom",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "........................... she arrives I will give her your message.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "As soon as",
                        "No sooner",
                        "Hardly"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The experience was .......................... painful ............................... recovery seemed difficult.",
                    "description": "So...that... expresses cause and effect. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "so... that",
                        "such...that",
                        "too...to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The girl ........................... cat was missing went from house to house looking for it.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "whom",
                        "who's",
                        "whose"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "It was …………………… a wonderful experience that I still remember it vividly.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "such"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": ".............................. did she arrive than I handed her the parcel.",
                    "description": "No sooner is used in a comparative structure with than.",
                    "answers": [
                        "No sooner",
                        "As soon as",
                        "Hardly"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She acts ............................. she was rich.",
                    "description": "As if and as though are used to say how a situation looks like. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "as if",
                        "as though",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She asked me ............................ there was anything she could do for me.",
                    "description": "Either if or whether can be used to introduce an yes/no question. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "if",
                        "whether",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}